brand.com 2014-02-18

# Privacy Policy : Brand.com™

**PRIVACY GUARANTEE**

We will never sell, rent, give or otherwise disclose to any third party any information that you may provide to us without your consent unless we are legally obliged to surrender this information by a subpoena or court order as part of an investigation into possible criminal activity.

**PRIVACY NOTICE**

Brand.com, its affiliates and suppliers take your privacy seriously. This notice describes our privacy policy. By visiting Brand.com, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Notice. 

Here are the types of information we gather. 

**Information You Give Us:** We receive and store any information you enter on our Web site or give us in any other way. We use the information that you provide for such purposes as responding to your requests, improving our schools, and communicating with you. 

**Automatic Information:** We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with us. For example, like many Web sites, we use "cookies," and we obtain certain types of information when your Web browser accesses Brand.com web site. 

**E-mail Communications:** To help us make e-mails more useful and interesting, we often receive a confirmation when you open e-mail from Brand.com if your computer supports such capabilities. We also compare our customer list to lists received from other companies, in an effort to avoid sending unnecessary messages to our customers. 

**Cookies:** Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser and to provide advanced features, keep track of your basket contents, etc.

Information about our customers is an important part of our business, and we are not in the business of selling it to others. We will release account and other personal information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with law; enforce or apply our Terms and Conditions and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of Brand.com, our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction. 

If you choose to visit Brand.com, your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Notice and our User Agreement, including limitations on damages, arbitration of disputes, and application of the law of the state Brand.com operates in. This Notice and the Terms and Conditions will change also, and use of information that we gather now is subject to the Privacy Notice in effect at the time of use. It is your responsibility to check our Web site frequently to see recent changes.
